Guide to the Freedom to Marry Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Program Files, 1973-2016; Series IV; 45.84; 113 boxes
  - Communication files, 1991-2010
    - Program commentary, 2003 November (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Protections of marriage support (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Race and marriage, 2006 (Box 119, Folder 18)
    - Reports and publications (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Resolution anti-marriage rights, 1995 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Resolution pre-Baehr, 1995 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Resolutions other version, 1994-1999 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Resources distributed, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Responding to "marriage harms children" argument roundtable, 2009 June 4-5 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Samiya A Bashir: Comm work plan, 2006 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Samiya A. Bashir: monthly reports, 2006 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Samiya A. Bashir: Steering committee meeting (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Service Employees International Union - AFL-CIO, 2005 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Stonewell Democrats, 2005 (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Tech assist/Federation summit, 2004 (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - The Matrix (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - The Nix Group, 2005 (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - The Time 100 - Evan Wolfson press kit - profiles, 2004 April (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Website, 2006 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Website, 2010 October 21 (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Partner organization files, 1995-2016
    - American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) too high a price the case against restricting gay parenting (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Activist: The times of Vito Russo, 1 (Box 147)
    - ADM bi-annual meeting, 2005 March (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - ADM bi-annual meeting, 2006 April (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - African-American community (Box 120, Folder 18)
    - Ann Thompson Cook publication, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - The Annual update of the American Civil Liberties Union's (ACLU) nationwide word on LGBT right and HIV/AIDS, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - API: Asian and Pacific Islanders equality (Box 120, Folder 19)
    - Arcus foundation annual report, 2005 (Box 120, Folder 20)
    - Arcus foundation annual report, 2006 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Arcus foundation annual report, 2007 (Box 120, Folder 19)
    - Astraea lesbian foundation for justice trends, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Astrea sponsorship (Box 120, Folder 22)
    - Atlanta black gay pride (Box 120, Folder 23)
    - Background readings conference on the interstate recognition of marriage, 1996 February 24 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Bible homosexuality - JM Worth, 2005 (Box 120, Folder 24)
    - Bienstar human services, 2005 (Box 120, Folder 25)
    - Bienstar proposal, 2005 (Box 120, Folder 26)
    - Breaking new ground horizons foundation annual, 2007 (Box 120, Folder 27)
    - Brother outside: The Life of Bayard Rustin, 1 (Box 148)
    - CAAF Asian equality (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Center for Genetics and Society committee on women, population and the environment, 1 (Box 149)
    - Civil marriage briefing binder, 2003 November; 3 (Box 89–91)
      - Civil marriage briefing binder, 2016-M-0040-0007; 1 (Box 89)
      - Civil marriage briefing binder, 2016-M-0040-0008; 1 (Box 90)
      - Civil marriage briefing binder, 2016-M-0040-0009; 1 (Box 91)
    - Civil marriage collaborative
      - 2003 funding cycle proposals to review, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 2-4)
      - 2006 funding cycle proposals for review (Box 121, Folder 5-7)
      - Committee meeting, 2005 January 12 (Box 121, Folder 8)
      - Committee meeting, 2005 June 24 (Box 121, Folder 9)
      - Committee meeting, 2008 November 12-13 (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - Committee meeting, 2009 January 30 (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - Committee meeting, 2009 June 9-10 (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - Committee meeting, 2007 June 27-28 (Box 123, Folder 1-2)
      - Committee meeting, 2007 November 7-8 (Box 123, Folder 3)
      - Committee meeting, 2007 January 30-31 (Box 123, Folder 4-5)
      - Committee meeting, 2008 June 18-19 (Box 123, Folder 6)
      - Committee meeting, 2009 October 22 (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - Committee meetings, 2010 February (Box 122, Folder 5)
      - Committee member meeting, 2006 January 11 (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - Docket meeting packet, 2011 February (Box 122, Folder 7)
      - Membership packet, circa 2008 (Box 122, Folder 8)
      - A project of the Proteus fund, 2006 June 2 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Children of Lesbians and Gay Everywhere (Colage), 2004-2005 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Communications workgroup (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Creating change, 2004 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Development - Vivek Tiwary, 2005 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - District of Columbia (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Documents de Travail: more or less together, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Drum major institute for public policy year in review, 2007 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Equal marriage.org: the Freedom to Marry Coalition of Massachusetts, 2004 December 11; 1 (Box 70, Folder 3, Box 150)
      - [no label information], 2016-M-0049-0019; 1 (Box 150)
    - Equal rights Washington (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Equality federation 2007 summer meeting (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Equality forum (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Equality Illinois, 2005 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Etc group presentation (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Evan Wolfson AGLP fryer award, 2010 October; 1 (Box 151)
    - Evan Wolfson book tour, 2004 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Family pride coalition corporate sponsorship packet, 2004 December (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Equality Federation: equality agenda, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Fact sheets (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Family pride, 2005 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Fenton (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Fenton communications tips (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Freedom to Marry regranting grid (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Freeheld (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Funders for Lesbian and gay issues Q-notes, 2004-2005 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Funders for gay and lesbian issues 'lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender and other queer grantmaking by US foundations, 2004 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Gill Action, 2009 July 30 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - GLBTQ Legal Advocates & Defenders (GLAD), 2001-2003 (Box 124, Folder 11-12)
    - GLBTQ Legal Advocates & Defenders Defeating DOMA (GLAD) (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - GLAAD (Gay & Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation) annual report, 2004 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - GLAAD (Gay & Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation) communications, 2005 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - GLAAD (Gay & Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation), 2005 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Golden Apple Academy, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Good News Articles/reference, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Grassroots Fundraising journal volume 24 number 5, 2005 September-October (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Guidelines for litigating same-sex marriage recognition cases, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Horizons foundation celebrates 25 years 2004 annual report (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Human Rights Campaign discussion, 2006 (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Human Rights Campaign, 2005-2006 (Box 124, Folder 16-18)
    - Human Rights Campaign answers to questions about equality (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Human Rights Campaign from state to state, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Human Rights Campaigns: Equality from state to state, 2004-2005 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Humans Rights Campaign message project, 2006 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - HRC's Standing up for Equality report and recent and pending marriage cases (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - I do. Who can't? ALF Silicon Valley Senior Fellows model leadership in this film by speaking out candidly about a civil rights issue of our day - equal marriage rights for same-sex couples, 1 (Box 152)
    - Illinois: Chicago commission on human relations, 2004 January 21 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - International gay and lesbian human rights commission annual report, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Interfaith alliance: same-gender marriage and religious freedom (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Ipsos - Public affairs, 2005 April 4-6 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Iraq and Afghanistan veterans of America presentations (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Jayme del Rosario - consultant (Box 124, Folder 20)
    - Jumping the broom (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Kathleen Oliva Freedom to Marry practicum, 2010 (Box 153)
    - Kings College London legal recognition of same-sex partnerships conference, 1999 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Lambda legal (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Lambda Legal: igualdad en el matrimonio (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Lambda model brief on Hawaii same-sex marriage, 1998 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Landscape (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Law and sexuality volume 14, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - League of cities, 2013 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Lesbian and Gay law notes, 2003 January-2004 December (Box 71, Folder 7-9)
    - Lesbian and Gay law notes, 2005 January-2006 December (Box 72, Folder 1-2)
    - Lesbian and gay law notes, 2007 January-2009 December (Box 72, Folder 3-5)
    - Lesbian and gay law notes, 2010 January-2011 November (Box 73, Folder 3-4)
    - Lesbian and gay law notes articles (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender and queer grantmaking by U.S. foundations, 2005 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender and queer grantmaking by U.S. foundation, 2009 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Llego, 2000 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Love makes a family (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Love makes a family marriage equality for same-sex couples: a Connecticut conversation, 2003 March 29 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - LGBT movement communications toolkit (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Lambda legal "second class citizens" annual report, 2005 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Marcha lesbica Mexico notebook, 2003 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Maricopa County Bar Association CLE class: is banning gay marriage constitutional? by Evan Wolfson, supplemental reading (Box 73, Folder 6-7)
    - Maricopa County Bar Association CLE class: is banning gay marriage constitutional? by Evan Wolfson, supplemental reading (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Maricopa County Bar Association: Is Banning Gay Marriage constitutional?, 2004 May 6 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Marriage coalition meeting, 2006 September 25 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Marriage equality California roadmap to equality: a Freedom to Marry educational guide, 2002 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Marriage matters Oregon fliers (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Marriage presentation (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Messaging National Center for Lesbian Rights (NCLR), 2005 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - MKE center POC position, 2006 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - The Mormon Proposition: Equality for Some, 1 (Box 92)
    - Out front Minnesota 2007 legislative handbook (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Movement advancement project LGBT movement communications Toolkit "Talking to the Moveable Middle Presentation", 2008 February (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) 2005 annual report "Leading by Example" (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - National Black Justice Coalition (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - The National Conference on LGBT Equality, 2008 February 6-10 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - The National Conference on LGBT Equality, Creating Change, 2010 February 3-7 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Forces: Creating Change Oakland, 2005 November 9-13 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force: Marriage equality resource notebook (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - National Gay Lesbian Task Force annual report, 2007 (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - National Latino Coalition for Justice (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - National Organization for Women (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - NBSC annual report, 2006-2007 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - National Center for Lesbian Rights (NCLR) 2008 giving campaign (Box 125, Folder 19)
    - National Center for Lesbian Rights (NCLR) annual report, 2007 (Box 125, Folder 20)
    - New Agora corporation, 2005 (Box 125, Folder 21)
    - National LGBTQ Task Force (NGLTF) (Box 125, Folder 22)
    - National LGBTQ Task Force (NGLTF) lease, 2005 (Box 125, Folder 23)
    - Northwest women's law center (Box 125, Folder 24)
    - National Organization for Women (NOW) conference, 2005 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - NYCFM meeting, 2002-2003 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - On the road to equality annual report, 2007 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Open Society Institute, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - OUTspoken families: Family pride speakers (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - PBK book promo, 2005 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Parents, Families, and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG), 1995 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Parents, Families, and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG), 1995 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Pride Foundation gratitude report, 2003-2004 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Print material distribution list, 2007 July (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Proteus fund, 2004 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Queer Asian Pacific Legacy conference, 2005 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Question one (rough): Flag on the Wall Productions J. Fox + J. Nubir, 1 (Box 154)
    - R platform media training, 2015 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Racial equality LGBTQ report card on racial equality, 2008 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Reform the platform, 2016 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Regranting memos (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Regranting
      - Kentucky Fairness Alliance Education Fund, 2004 (Box 126, Folder 14)
      - 2004-A: Lambda legal New Mexico (Box 126, Folder 15)
      - 2004-B: Religious institute (Box 126, Folder 16)
      - 2004-C: Basic Rights Oregon (Box 126, Folder 17)
      - 2004-D: Coalition for equality New Mexico (Box 126, Folder 18)
      - 2004-E: Llego (Box 126, Folder 19)
      - 2004-F: Freedom to Marry Foundation Massachusetts (Box 126, Folder 20)
      - 2004-G: Freedom to Marry California (F2MCA) (Box 126, Folder 21)
      - 2004-H: Federation summit (Box 127, Folder 1)
      - 2004-I: National Black Justice Coalition (NBJC) (Box 127, Folder 2)
      - 2004-J: United Church of Christ coalition (Box 127, Folder 3)
      - 2004-K: Public interest (Box 127, Folder 4)
      - 2004-L: National conference for comm. and justice (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - 2004-M: ESPA (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - 2004-N: National Black Justice Coalition (NBJC) community development meeting (Box 127, Folder 7)
      - 2004-O: Evebrite (Box 127, Folder 8)
      - 2004-P: BREF (Box 127, Folder 9-10)
      - 2004-R: Institute for Gay and Lesbian Strategic Studies (IGLSS) (Box 127, Folder 11)
      - 2004-S: Institute for Gay and Lesbian Strategic Studies (IGLSS) (Connecticut, Massachusetts, New Mexico) (Box 127, Folder 12)
      - 2004-*: National Black Justice Coalition (NBJC) ads (Box 127, Folder 13)
      - 2005-1: Garden State equality (Box 127, Folder 14)
      - 2005-2: ICLCM - Interdenominational conference (Box 127, Folder 15)
      - 2005-3: National Black Justice Coalition (NBJC) (Box 127, Folder 16)
      - 2005-A: Northwest women's law center (Box 127, Folder 17)
      - 2005-C: ESPA (Box 127, Folder 18)
      - 2005-D: Equality Maryland (Box 127, Folder 19)
      - 2005-E: Highlander/Song (Box 127, Folder 20)
      - 2005-F: Universal Fellowship of Metropolitan Community Churches (UFMCC) (Box 127, Folder 21)
      - 2005-H: United Church of Christ coalition (Box 127, Folder 22)
      - 2005-G: AFL-CIO (Box 128, Folder 1)
      - 2005-I: California conference, 2002-2005 (Box 128, Folder 2)
      - 2005-J: Christians for Equality (Wisconsin) (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - 2005-K: NBJC - National Black Justice Coalition, 2006 (Box 128, Folder 4)
      - 2005-L: Marriage Equality Rhode Island (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - 2005-M: Religious coalition for equality (Washington) (Box 128, Folder 6)
      - 2005-N: Equality California institute (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - 2005-P: California council of churches (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - 2005-Q: Bienestar (Box 128, Folder 9)
      - 2005-R: United Church of Christ (Box 128, Folder 10)
      - 2005-T: AAMOE (POC), 2005-2006 (Box 128, Folder 11)
      - 2005-U: NBJC [National Black Justice Coalition] black church (Box 128, Folder 12)
      - 2005-W: Turtle Time productions, 2004-2005 (Box 128, Folder 13)
      - 2005-X: California Faith for Equality (CFE), 2005-2006 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Religious coalition for equality coalition, 2006 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Republican letters, 2010 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Richard Nathan anti-homophobic trusts final report (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - The Right to Loves (Gene Lees and Lalo Schifrin) 1) Peggy Lee 2) Tony Bennett 3) Rebecca Parris, 1 (Box 155)
    - Same-sex marriage a civil debate, 2004 February 24; 1 (Box 156)
    - Sample annual reports (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - Say It Loud the task force, 2005 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - SC Equality coalition, 2006 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Scripture and Marriage Equality, 2006; 1 (Box 157)
    - Sonnenschein Nath and Rosenthal LLP: commemorating 100 years of partnering for progress, 2006-2007 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - SonnenscheinNath Rosentha (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Soros foundations network report, 2007 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Soulforce (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - South African law cases, 2005 December 1 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Spin works by Robert Bray, 2002 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Stay close/Parents, Families, and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG), 1995 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Storycenter, 2005 (Box 129, Folder 6-7)
    - Strauss radio strategies, 2002 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Talking about adoptions and gay parents (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Talking Points - Freedom to Marry, 2005 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Talking with Latinos and Hispanics about LGB equality journal, 2011 August (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Talking points - partners, 2005 (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Turtletime production (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - A Time to Seek: study guide on sexual and gender diversity (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - A Time to Seek: study guide on sexual and gay diversity (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Conference of mayors, 2013 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - V CAA, 2005 (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Varnum v. Brien briefs and decisions (Box 75, Folder 6-7)
    - Vermont Freedom to Marry task force regrant final report, 2006 (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Web of Truth 2008 annual report (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Young Conservatives New Hampshire, Iowa, Nevada, South Carolina, Michigan, Texas, Ohio (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Young Conservatives for the Freedom to Marry media guide, 2012 (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - Young Conservatives for the Freedom to Marry, 2013 (Box 129, Folder 18)
    - Zuna (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - Zuna institute - National Black Lesbian Conference (NBLC) (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Publications, 1973-2015
    - 2003 End-of-Year report (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Addendum to Joint Committee Report on Same-Sex Marriage, 2002 January 22 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - A Right to Same-Sex Marriage Under International Law, Sadtler, Edward H., 1999 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - An Ally's Guide to Talking About Marriage for Same Sex Couples (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - A Right to Same Sex Marriage Under International Law, Sadtler, Edward H., 1999 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - At the Crossroads: National Black Justice Coalition report, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Chapter 2-7 galley copy (Box 130)
    - Civil Marriage for Gary Couples brochure (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Color codes - E-Update, 2006 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Columbia Journal of Gender and Law, 2015 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Committee on Civil Rights annual meeting, 2002 January 23 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - The Constitution of the United States (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Directory of Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Services and Resources, 2000 June (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Diversified Print Solutions (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Employment Discrimination, Law and Litigation, volume 2 Rossein, Merrick T., 1993 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Evan Wolfson author bio (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Familia Es Familia brochures (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Family Policy Issues Affecting Gay-Lesbian, Bisexual and Transgender Families (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - The Federal Lawyer volume 44 number 8, 1997 September (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Freedom to Marry Democrats: Say I Do stickers (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Freedom to Marry brochures (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Freedom to Marry pamphlets (Box 76, Folder 12-13)
    - Freedom to Marry petition sample (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - From Wrongs to Rights 1973-1999, Yang, Alan (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - The Gay and Lesbian Review Worldwide, 2001 January-February (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Gaydar Directory of Authoritative Resources, 1999-2000 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Harvard Journal of Law and Public Policy volume 14 number 1, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Howard Law Journal volume 51: issue 1, 2007 fall (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Human Rights volume 21 number 3, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - IGCSS Technical Report, 1998 October (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Just the Facts About Sexual Orientation and Youth (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Journal of Gay and Lesbian Mental Health volume 13 number 3, 2009 July-September (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Ethos: Journal of the Society for Psychological Anthropology volume 39 number 4, 2011 December (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Jumping the Broom: A Black Perspective on Same-Sex Marriage, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Lavender Law 2000 attendees (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Law & Sexuality volume 14, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Legislating Equality (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Directory of Services and Resources, 2003 June (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Letter to George Bush, 2001 November 27 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - The Little Black Book, LAMBDA Legal Defense Fund (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Marriage Inequality in the State of Maryland, 2006 February (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Marriage: It's Past, Present and Future, Besant, Annie (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Media Protocol, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - MEM Campaign (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Mixed Blessings, Organized Religion and Gay and Lesbian Americans in 1998 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Mayor for the Freedom to Marry stickers (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - More or Less Together: Levels of Legal Consequences of Marriage, Cohabitation and Registered Partnership for Different Sex and Same-Sex Partners, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - National Black Justice Coalition pamphlets (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - National Director of Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Community Centers brochure, 1997 November (Box 77, Folder 18)
    - New York Magazine, 1999 August 16 (Box 77, Folder 19)
    - New York Magazine, 2000 August 21 (Box 77, Folder 20)
    - New York State Bar Association Committee on Civil Rights, 2002 January 23 (Box 77, Folder 21)
    - New York University Review of Law and Social Change volume XXI number 3, 1994-1995 (Box 77, Folder 22)
    - New York University Review of Law and Social Change volume 37 number 1, 2013 (Box 77, Folder 23)
    - Next Magazine, 1999 September 3 (Box 77, Folder 24)
    - Non-Gay Placements, 2005 (Box 77, Folder 25)
    - No On Proposition 22 (Box 77, Folder 26)
    - National Lesbian and Gay Law Association membership directory, 2000 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - National Lesbian and Gay Law Association membership directory, 2001 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - NYANSAPO (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - One Year of Marriage Equality, 2005 September 8 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Out (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Pocket Guide to the Constitution of the United States (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Pride Magazine 14, 2014 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Proposition 22 and Same-Gender Marriage: A Study Resource for Congregations (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Publications, 2005 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Press Release receipts, 2005 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - QLR: The Freedom to Marry: Our Struggle for the Map of the Country volume 16 number 1 and 2, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Radio (Box 78, Folder 12)